export const Questions = [
    { 
        prompt: "Who is the Seal of the Prophets?",
        opA: "Ibrahim,",
        opB: "Ayub",
        opC: "Isse",
        opD: "Muhammad, may God bless him and grant him peace",
        Answer: "opD",
     
    },


    { 
        prompt: "The prayer that has no voluntary voluntary prayers after it ?",
        opA: "Al-fajr praye ",
        opB: "Asr prayer",
        opC: "Salat Aduher",
        opD: "None",
        Answer: "opB",
     
    },


    { 
        prompt: "Who is the prophet who was called the Word of God?",
        opA: "Prophet Muhammad, peace be upon him",
        opB: "Adam",
        opC: "Musse cs",
        opD: "Isse",
        Answer: "opC",
     
    },

    { 
        prompt: "How many daily prayers are there in Islam?",
        opA: "1",
        opB: "4",
        opC: "3",
        opD: "5",
        Answer: "opD",
     
    },
    { 
        prompt: "what day is the Muslims special day?",
        opA: "Sunday",
        opB: "Friday",
        opC: "Tuesday",
        opD: "Wednesday",
        Answer: "opB",
     
    },

    { 
        prompt: "How many names does Allah have?",
        opA: "99",
        opB: "612",
        opC: "3",
        opD: "1",
        Answer: "opA",
     
    },

    { 
        prompt: "What is the surah without which prayer is not valid?",
        opA: "Surah Al-Falaq.",
        opB: "Surat Al-Asr",
        opC: "Surah Al-Fatihah ",
        opD: "None",
        Answer: "opC",
     
    },

    
    { 
        prompt: "Maghrib prayer: how many rak'ahs?",
        opA: "1 ",
        opB: "None",
        opC: "3",
        opD: "7",
        Answer: "opB",
     
    },

    { 
        prompt: "The companion who was called the Secretary of the Imams....",
        opA: "Abu Bakr",
        opB: "Bilal bin Rabah",
        opC: "Abu Ubaidah bin Al-Jarrah",
        opD: "7Othman bin Affan ",
        Answer: "opC",
     
    },

    { 
        prompt: "The companion who was called the Secretary of the Imams....",
        opA: "Abu Bakr, may Allah be pleased with him",
        opB: "Bilal bin Rabah may God be pleased with him",
        opC: "Abu Ubaidah bin Al-Jarrah, may God be pleased with him",
        opD: "Othman bin Affan may Allah be pleased with him ",
        Answer: "opC",
     
    },
    

    
];

